http://www.lemonlawyers.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyLemonLawUSA.org seeks to protect your privacy. Accordingly, we will respect all information you provide through the LemonLawUSA.org website. LemonLawUSA.org will not sell or disclose personally identifiable information about you to unaffiliated third parties except in accordance with this "Privacy Policy".Information Collection
LemonLawUSA.org’s website collects certain information about visitors, even when they are not logged in. LemonLawUSA.org may record your IP address, the URLs of the websites and pages you visit (before, during and after your visit to LemonLawUSA.org website), the times and dates of such visits, information about the computer hardware and software you use and other information that may be available. Also, LemonLawUSA.org may place "cookies" on your computer to recognize you on return visits to enable LemonLawUSA.org to enhance your browsing experience, as well as to collect additional information about you. You may adjust your browser settings or use other means to prevent cookies from being placed on your computer, but doing so may result in reduced functionality and a less personalized browsing experience. LemonLawUSA.org may ask you to provide additional information about yourself, including your name, contact information, the organization you come from and certain other information that LemonLawUSA.org may use to identify you. If you choose not to provide such information, you may not be permitted to access certain LemonLawUSA.org website features, content or services. Information Use LemonLawUSA.org uses the information that it collects about you to improve your browsing experience by personalizing LemonLawUSA.org websites to your interest, and also to help LemonLawUSA.org select content and services you may find interesting and useful. Information about the content you visit and services you use may be used alone or in conjunction with information collected from other users to help us tailor the LemonLawUSA.org website, together with sponsored products and/or services, to better suit the needs and interests of you and other users. Information you provide may be used as part of LemonLawUSA.org’s effort to keep you informed about news, events, and selected products and services that may be of interest to you. In some cases, LemonLawUSA.org may contact you with information from carefully selected third parties, but LemonLawUSA.org will not provide information to third parties for such purposes. In other cases, your information might be shared with a third party pursuant to a process that contemplates such sharing but which you knowingly initiate. LemonLawUSA.org reserves the right to disclose any information that it obtains through the LemonLawUSA.org’s website to appropriate governmental or regulatory authorities, if required by law or any governmental agency with the authority to request or demand such information. Information Transfers From time to time, LemonLawUSA.org may disclose information about you to carefully selected goods and service providers that LemonLawUSA.org may engage to host or sponsor the LemonLawUSA.org website or to provide other services. LemonLawUSA.org will require all such goods and service providers, hosts or sponsors to use the information solely to provide the specified goods and/or services, and otherwise to conform to the requirements of this Privacy Policy. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, LemonLawUSA.org will not provide your information to third parties for any other purpose, including marketing. Additional Services From time to time, LemonLawUSA.org may offer additional goods or services on the LemonLawUSA.org website. In some cases additional goods or services may be subject to alternative terms of use (as identified by LemonLawUSA.org), and your use of any such goods or services will constitute your acceptance of such alternative terms of use. Unless otherwise stated, such alternative terms of use shall apply to supplement this Agreement and in the context of any conflicting terms, this Agreement shall govern with respect to LemonLawUSA.org’s websites, content and goods or services, excepting only those goods or services which are expressly covered, and then only to the extent so expressly covered, by such alternative terms. Information Through Website Is Not Secure. Any information sent to LemonLawUSA.org by Internet e-mail or through the website is not necessarily secure. Any information you send LemonLawUSA.org over the Internet, either through LemonLawUSA.org’s website or via email is done at your own risk. Sending Information Does Not Form an Attorney - Client Relationship. Transmission of information to or from this website does not create an attorney-client relationship between you, LemonLawUSA.org or any of our sponsors, hosts and/or advertisers, nor is it intended to do so. The receipt by or transmission of the website, in part or in whole, and/or any communication with us via Internet e-mail or other means through this website does not constitute or create an attorney-client relationship between us, our sponsors, hosts, and/or advertisers and any transmitters or recipients.
Contact Us
Sponsored by Allen Stewart P.C. Go to the websiteContact Us 866-440-2460 Contact Us
